[ { "id": 0, 
    "question": "Have the new semantic tags in HTML5 replaced the &lt;div&gt; and &lt;span&gt; tags?", 
	"correctAnswer": "a", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter":"a", "value": "No. However, there are cases where the new tags are more appropriate."},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "No. div and span should still be used as before."},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "Yes. div and span are now deprecated."},
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "Yes. div and span tags are now obsolete. They should not be used."} ]
  },
  
  { "id": 1, 
    "question": "Does HTML 5 allow more than one &lt;heading&gt; element per page?", 
	"correctAnswer": "c", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter":"a", "value": "There is only one such element and it holds the page metadata and links to external resources"},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "No. The page should only contain one heading element, typically at the top of the page."},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "Yes. A page may contain multiple heading elements to introduce different sections."},
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "Yes. But this is only true when the heading elements occur within an article element."} ]
  },
  
  { "id" : 2,
    "question": "Is there any reason why you shouldn't use &lt;input type = \"e-mail\"&gt;?", 
	"correctAnswer": "c", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter":"a", "value": "It requires that the pattern for an e-mail address should be specified manually, which makes it redundant."},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "No. This input type works well in any scenario and will effectively validate e-mail addresses."},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "A problem for some users is that it will not always handle non-Latin characters correctly."},
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "The input type is now deprecated, so it should be avoided."} ]
  },
  
  { "id" : 3,
    "question": "What happens if an input type is used which is not supported by a certain browser?", 
	"correctAnswer": "b", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter":"a", "value": "The browser usually crashes, making it impossible for the user to use the page"},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "The input will still work but the browser will treat it as a text input"},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "An error message will be displayed to the user and it will not be possible to use the input"},
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "The input element will not be displayed."} ]
  },
  
    
  { "id" : 4,
    "question": "What is the purpose of the &lt;section&gt; element?", 
	"correctAnswer": "a", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter":"a", "value": "It is similar to the div element, but more specific, since it groups content which is related by a certain theme."},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "It is used only as a child of an &lt;article&gt and groups different sections of the article element."},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "It replaces the div element in HTML5 and is used in the layout of the page."},
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "It is used to group different types of inputs in forms into logical sections"} ]
  },
  
  { "id" : 5,
    "question": "Which of the following is an example of a situation where an &lt;article&gt; could be nested within another &lt;article&gt;?",
	"correctAnswer": "d", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter":"a", "value": "This is not the intended use of &lt;article&gt;. Article elements should never be nested within other article elements."},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "It is a valid approach for dividing an article into different parts with different headings"},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "Both b and d are correct."},
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "This may be done when the inner article is related to the outer one, although the inner one could exist independently."} ]
  },
  
  { "id" : 6,
    "question": "What format does the color input type use to store the color value?", 
	"correctAnswer": "c", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter":"a", "value": "RGB (Eg. (255, 0, 0) )"},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "HSL (Eg. (0, 100%, 50%) )"},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "Hexadecimal (Eg. #ff0000)" },
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "Named color (Eg. \"red\")"} ]
  },
  
  { "id" : 7,
    "question": "How do you control the granularity of the selector in &lt;input type = \"range\"&gt; ? ", 
	"correctAnswer": "b", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter":"a", "value": "The increment is always by one and it is not possible to change this."},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "This is done by setting the \"step\" attribute in the input tag to the desired amount."},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "The increment is determined by changing the width property in the associated stylesheet or directly on the input element."},
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "This is done by setting the \"min\" and \"max\" attributes on the element, so the browser can determine the appropriate granularity."} ]
  },
  
  { "id" : 8,
    "question": "What approach is used to handle differences in local data and time notations across different regions when storing input data in the datetime-local input type?", 
	"correctAnswer": "d", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter":"a", "value": "Different formats are used, based on the user's locale which is obtained from the operating system. "},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "There is no standard approach since different browsers use different formats for storing datetime-local value"},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "This type uses the North American format which starts with month (Eg. 10-25-2017T05:30)"},
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "A universal format is used to store input, starting with year in descending order (Eg. 2017-10-25T05:30)"} ]
  },
  
  { "id" : 9,
    "question": "HTML5 input validation is very convenient. But is it safe to rely on this alone when storing data?", 
	"correctAnswer": "d", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter":"a", "value": "Yes, it is safe in most cases. But it is sometimes necessary to use additional validation with JavaScript."},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "Yes it is safe. Additional validation is redundant."},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "No. JavaScript should always be used to validate data on the client before sending it to the server."},
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "No. The server must validate data as well, since validation on the client is not secure."} ]
  }
  
]
				   